http://illusionsetc.blogspot.com/2004/01/privacy-policy.html

skip to main
|
skip to sidebar
Description
Presented here is a vast gallery of many different forms of Optical Illusions. Whether these optical illusions are conveyed through fractals, photographs, architecture, art, or old fashioned pen and ink, they are bound to remind you that "seeing is not believing."
Caution!!!! Some of the optical illusions on this blog may cause dizziness or possibly epileptic seizures. The latter happens when the brain can't handle the conflicting information from your two eyes. If you start feeling unwell when using this website, immediately cover one eye with your hand and then leave the page. Do not close your eyes because that can make the attack worse.
Fractal of the Day
Provided By Sprott's Fractal Gallery
Wednesday
Privacy Policy for Optical Illusions Etc...
If you require any more information or have any questions about our privacy policy, please feel free to contact us by email at illusionsetc@gmail.com.At Optical Illusions Etc..., the privacy of our visitors is of extreme importance to us. This privacy policy document outlines the types of personal information is received and collected by Optical Illusions Etc... and how it is used.Log FilesLike many other Web sites, Optical Illusions Etc... makes use of log files. The information inside the log files includes internet protocol ( IP ) addresses, type of browser, Internet Service Provider ( ISP ), date/time stamp, referring/exit pages, and number of clicks to analyze trends, administer the site, track user’s movement around the site, and gather demographic information. IP addresses, and other such information are not linked to any information that is personally identifiable.Cookies and Web BeaconsOptical Illusions Etc... does use cookies to store information about visitors preferences, record user-specific information on which pages the user access or visit, customize Web page content based on visitors browser type or other information that the visitor sends via their browser.Some of our advertising partners may use cookies and web beacons on our site. Our advertising partners include Google Adsense, Chitka, Kontera.These third-party ad servers or ad networks use technology to the advertisements and links that appear on Optical Illusions Etc... send directly to your browsers. They automatically receive your IP address when this occurs. Other technologies ( such as cookies, JavaScript, or Web Beacons ) may also be used by the third-party ad networks to measure the effectiveness of their advertisements and / or to personalize the advertising content that you see.Optical Illusions Etc... has no access to or control over these cookies that are used by third-party advertisers.You should consult the respective privacy policies of these third-party ad servers for more detailed information on their practices as well as for instructions about how to opt-out of certain practices. Optical Illusions Etc's privacy policy does not apply to, and we cannot control the activities of, such other advertisers or web sites.If you wish to disable cookies, you may do so through your individual browser options. More detailed information about cookie management with specific web browsers can be found at the browsers' respective websites.
Optical Illusions Posted by Walt |
permalink |
Labels:
Privacy Policy
0
comments:
Post a Comment |
Random Illusion
Next Post
Previous Post
Home
Subscribe to:
Post Comments (Atom)
Copyright NoticeThe documents distributed here have been presented on this blog in the spirit of providing an entertaining venue to educate those interested in optical illusions.
All Flckr.com photos are presented here via Flckr's "blog this" feature. This feature is enabled by each artist on Flckr. If you find material here that belongs to you and you would like to have it removed or credited please contact me and I will gladly follow your wishes.
Copyright and all rights therein are maintained by the authors or by other copyright holders. It is understood that all persons copying this information will adhere to the terms and constraints invoked by each author's copyright. These works may not be reposted without the explicit permission of the copyright holder.
Search
Web
This Blog
Home
Site Map
Privacy Policy
Submit Optical Illusion!
Reality Carnival
Blogroll Me!
Featured...
March 2009 (3)
June 2007 (1)
May 2007 (4)
April 2007 (4)
March 2007 (4)
February 2007 (3)
January 2007 (4)
December 2006 (4)
November 2006 (4)
October 2006 (4)
September 2006 (3)
August 2006 (30)
July 2006 (31)
June 2006 (25)
May 2006 (28)
April 2006 (24)
January 2006 (5)
December 2005 (9)
November 2005 (13)
October 2005 (13)
September 2005 (13)
August 2005 (20)
July 2005 (24)
June 2005 (18)
May 2005 (11)
April 2005 (11)
March 2005 (16)
February 2005 (17)
January 2005 (23)
December 2004 (37)
November 2004 (14)
October 2004 (1)
September 2004 (2)
August 2004 (1)
July 2004 (1)
May 2004 (2)
April 2004 (1)
February 2004 (4)
January 2004 (21)
October 2003 (3)
hit counter
Optical Illusions Store
